Are you a hopeless romantic?
你是一个无可救药的浪漫主义者吗？
Do you get excited by the idea of falling in love with the man or woman of your dreams?
你会不会因为爱上梦中情人的想法而兴奋不已？
Does watching a romcom or a period drama on TV make you cry?
在电视上看一部浪漫爱情喜剧或年代剧会不会让你落泪呢？
Or are you someone who thinks romance is based on an idealised view of reality that doesn't really exist?
又或者，你是否认为浪漫是基于一种并不存在的理想化的现实？
Well, you could be right!
嗯，你也许是对的！
I'm no romantic and more of a realist - taking a more practical approach to love - maybe that's why I never had many girlfriends!
我不是一个浪漫主义者，更多的是一个现实主义者——对爱情采取更现实的态度——也许这就是为什么我从来没有过很多女朋友！
But if you really are expecting the kind of love that makes your heart flutter with happiness you may be disappointed.
但是如果你真的期待那种能让你的心因幸福而怦怦直跳的爱情，你可能会失望的。
Our expectation of what romance is, probably originated from the Romantic period - an artistic, literary, musical and intellectual movement that originated in Europe in the 18th Century.
我们对浪漫的期待，很可能源自浪漫主义时期——这是一场18世纪起源于欧洲的艺术、文学、音乐和思想运动。
The notion of falling in love, getting married and living happily ever after were culturally held ideas formed during this period and still exist today.
坠入爱河、结婚并从此过上幸福生活的观念是在这个时期形成的文化观念，并且一直延续到今天。
Of course there's nothing wrong with liking the idea of romance; it makes us feel good — but we must be careful not to use it as a benchmark for our own relationships.
当然，喜欢浪漫的想法并没有错；它让我们感觉良好——但我们必须小心，不要把它当作我们自己恋爱关系的衡量基准。
This idealised version of love leaves out the nitty-gritty of real-life relationships.
这种理想化的爱情版本忽略了现实生活中恋爱关系的具体细节。
There's usually work, finances and other stresses of everyday life to deal with.
通常还有工作、财务以及日常生活中的其他压力需要处理。
You can't expect romantic gestures like a bunch of red roses every day — there are bills to pay!
你不能指望每天都有像一束红玫瑰这样的浪漫举动——毕竟还有账单要付呢！
Many popular love stories end at the point where the characters get together or tie the knot.
许多流行的爱情故事都在男女主角在一起或结婚的时候就结束了。
That puts the focus on finding someone special.
这把重点放在了找到那个特别的人上。
But very few show us how to keep that perfect catch over a long period of time.
但很少有故事向我们展示如何在很长一段时间内留住那个理想伴侣。
A relationship is hard work.
维持一段恋爱关系是很不容易的。
It's frustrating, messy and can be emotionally damaging.
它会让人沮丧、混乱，而且可能会在情感上造成伤害。
If you're still convinced romance isn't dead, how will you ever find it?
如果你仍然坚信浪漫并没有消亡，那你要如何才能找到它呢？
Historian and TV presenter Lucy Worsley thinks nowadays, any idea of romance is dying because it has become "too easy" to meet new people via dating apps.
历史学家兼电视节目主持人露西·沃斯利认为，如今，任何关于浪漫的概念都在逐渐消逝，因为通过约会应用程序结识新人变得“太容易”了。
She told the BBC the "slow exquisite torture of love in Jane Austen novels no longer existed in the age of Grindr and Tinder [apps]."
她告诉英国广播公司：“简·奥斯汀小说中那种缓慢而美妙的爱情煎熬在Grindr和Tinder（约会应用程序）时代已经不复存在了。”
Perhaps romance is best left to the movies - a fantasy that makes us feel good - and instead concentrate on finding a good and healthy relationship, with all its ups and downs, but with lots of love.
也许浪漫最好还是留在电影里——那是一种能让我们感觉良好的幻想——而我们应该专注于寻找一段美好且健康的恋爱关系，这段关系起起伏伏，但却充满了爱。
Do you believe romance is really dead?
你相信浪漫真的存在吗？